Okay.
حسناً
♫ Strolling along in Central Park ♫
♫ مشياً على طول السنترال بارك ♫
♫ Everyone's out today ♫
♫ كل شخص في الخارج اليوم ♫
♫ The daisies and dogwoods are all in bloom ♫
♫ الاقحوانات والزهور كلها تتفتح ♫
♫ Oh, what a glorious day ♫
♫ أوه ، ياله من يوم مجيد ♫
♫ For picnics and Frisbees and roller skaters, ♫
♫ للنزهات ،اللعب بالأقراص الطائرة والمتزلجين ♫
♫ Friends and lovers and lonely sunbathers ♫
♫ للأصدقاء والعشاق والمتشمسون لوحدهم ♫
♫ Everyone's out in merry Manhattan in January ♫
♫ كل شخص بالخارج ، خلال مانهاتن السعيدة في يناير ♫
(Laughter) (Applause)
(تصفيق)
♫ I brought the iced tea; ♫
♫ أحضرت معي الشاي المثلج : ♫
♫ Did you bring the bug spray? ♫
♫ هل احضرت معكي مبيد الحشرات ♫
♫ The flies are the size of your head ♫
♫ لأن الذباب بحجم اليد ♫
♫ Next to the palm tree, ♫
♫ بجوار شجرة النخيل ، ♫
♫ Did you see the 'gators ♫
♫ هل رأيتي التماسيح ♫
♫ Looking happy and well fed? ♫
♫ تبدو سعيدة وبصحة جيدة ؟ ♫
♫ Everyone's out in merry Manhattan in January ♫
♫ كل شخص بالخارج ، خلال مانهاتن السعيدة في يناير ♫
(Whistling)
(تصفير)
Everyone!
جميعاً !
♫ My preacher said, ♫
♫ قال لي واعظي ♫
♫ Don't you worry ♫
♫ لا يجب عليك أن تقلقي ♫
♫ The scientists have it all wrong ♫
♫ لأن العلماء مخطئون ♫
♫ And so, who cares it's winter here? ♫
♫ إذاً ، من يأبه إذا كان الوقت شتاء هنا؟ ♫
♫ And I have my halter-top on ♫
♫ مادمت أرتدي صديريتي الصيفية ♫
♫ I have my halter-top on ♫
♫ أرتدي صديريتي الصيفية ♫
♫ Everyone's out in merry Manhattan in January. ♫
♫ كل شخص بالخارج ، خلال مانهاتن السعيدة في يناير ♫
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Chris Anderson: Jill Sobule!
كريس أندرسن : جيل سيبيول